긴급 경보: 포자 폭풍 접근중
NPCD(질병 관리국)
NOTE [Music]
스페인 질병 관리국
NOTE If you are seeing this video, you are
currently experiencing a Spore storm.
이 영상을 보고 계신다면, 해당 지역에
포자 폭풍이 발생 중이라는 의미입니다.
NOTE This is a newly occurring weather phenomenon.
이것은 새롭게 발생한 기상 현상입니다.
NOTE Heavy clouds are approaching your location
carrying billions of mycopsychosis spores.
수십억 개의 마이코사이코시스 포자가 포함된
짙은 구름이 귀하의 위치로 접근 중입니다.
NOTE They travel through the air.
A single spore is enough to infect a host
포자는 공기를 통해 전파됩니다.
단 하나의 포자만으로도 숙주를 감염시킬 수 있습니다.
NOTE Make sure you stay inside. Lock your doors and windows.
And don't exit under any circumstances.
반드시 실내에 머무르십시오. 문과 창문을 잠그십시오.
어떤 상황에서도 절대 밖으로 나가지 마십시오.
NOTE Wait until the storm passes.
Try not to succumb to fear and wait patiently.
폭풍이 지나갈 때까지 기다리십시오.
두려움에 굴복하지 말고 인내심을 가지고 기다리십시오.
NOTE 10 [Noise] 0052440 to 0053440
NOTE How to identify the infection.
감염 식별 방법.
NOTE Mycopsychosis spores can enter your bloodstream through
your lungs, open cut or any exposed mucous membrane.
마이코사이코시스 포자는 폐, 찢어진 상처, 또는
노출된 점막을 통해 혈류로 침투할 수 있습니다.
NOTE Symptoms only take a couple of minutes to appear.
잠복기는 없습니다. 증상은 단 몇 분 만에 발현됩니다.
NOTE Stages of the infection.
감염의 단계 구분.
NOTE Stage One. General confussion.
1단계. 일반적 혼란.
NOTE The symptoms are sweating, fever, headache, vomit.
Once a host starts to develop these symptoms there is no possible cure.
주요 증상으로 발한, 발열, 두통, 구토증세를 보입니다.
이러한 증상을 보이기 시작했다면 치료법은 없습니다.
NOTE 17 [Music] 0130120 to 0132320
NOTE Once a host starts to develop these symptoms, they should immediately
contact local Health authorities and wait for further instructions
감염자가 이러한 증상을 보이기 시작한다면, 즉시 지역
보건 당국에 연락하고 추가 지시를 기다려야 합니다.
NOTE Stage Two. Take over.
2단계. 장악.
NOTE The symptoms are severe paranoia, visual and auditory
hallucinations, uncontrollably desire to socialize.
주요 증상으로 심각한 편집증, 환각 및 환청,
'통제할 수 없는 사회적 교류 욕구'를 보입니다.
NOTE The spores had arrived to the host's brain
and they are starting to take control.
이는, 포자가 숙주의 이미 뇌에 도달했으며
통제권을 장악하기 시작했다는 신호입니다.
NOTE 22 [Noise] 000202000 to 000202500
NOTE Stage Three. Activation
3단계. 활성화.
NOTE The symptoms are uncontrollably desired to go to a high place.
The spores had reproduced in the host body.
증상은 높은 곳으로 가고 싶은 통제 불가능한 욕구입니다.
포자가 숙주의 체내에서 증식됩니다.
NOTE The infection has reached its maturity stage.
이는 감염이 성숙 단계에 도달했다는 의미입니다.
NOTE Stage Four. Blooming.
4단계. 개화.
NOTE For further survivability please follow your Spore storm
survival manual, or check the following webpage.
생존 확률을 높이기 위해, 포자 폭풍 생존 매뉴얼을
따르거나 다음 웹페이지를 확인하십시오.
NOTE 28 [Music] 000234500 to 000237000
NOTE 29 [Beep] 000237000 to 000242000